# Mehrdad Ghasemkhani



linkedin.com/in/mehrdad-ghasemkhani



https://mehrdad-drpc.github.io/



mehrdad.pc@gmail.com



+989385200818

### Summary

Experienced VoIP/DevOps Engineer high focus on CPaaS and UCaaS, with a demonstrated history of working in the internet telephony industry. Skilled in SQL and noSQL Databases, like Mysql, Postgres, Apache ChouchDB, Functional and Object-Oriented Programming, like Erlang, Java and Python. Linux and ShellScripting. DevOps tools, like Git, CI/CD, Docker, Ansible. VoIP tools, like Kamailio, Asterisk, Freeswitch. Some TCP/IP protocol like HTTP, HTTPS, SIP, RTP, SDP, NAT, IP, TCP, UDP. Strong engineering professional graduated from Shamsipour and Raja university.

### Experience



### DevOps Engineer

Respina Networks & Beyond

Feb 2020 - Present (6 months +)

- # Cloud Telecommunication Technology CPaaS, UCaaS
- # Session Initiation Protocol
- # Kamailio SIP-Server
- # Asterisk/Freeswitch Softswitch
- # Maintainer of own SIP-Trunk
- # Maintainer of own HostedPBX
- # Docker/ Docker-Compose
- # Load Balancing and High Availability

### Backend Developer

Respina Networks & Beyond

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020 (9 months)

- # Develop ARI(Asterisk RESTful Interface) with python and Django
- # Develop Asterisk Call Manager Over The ARI

# Python Developer

Kara Tadbir Hooshmand Kish

Jul 2017 - Jun 2018 (1 year)

# Analyzed, designed and developed of a RESTful API with Python, Flask, gREST and Neo4j, PostgreSQL,

Kong, ... to serve 2.5 million subscribers

- # Experienced with pair-programming of project with junior/senior developers
- # Hands-on experience with many of the latest cutting-edge technologies
- # Provided regular and effective progress updates to my-head
- # Wrote some python's unit-test and integration-test to develop CI/CD

### C Developer

AVA Communication Industries Co.

Sep 2016 - Jan 2017 (5 months)

# Develop Server-Side Socket via C

# Develop Client-Side Socket via Javascript/PHP

# **Education**



# Shamsipour Technical and Vocational College

Associate's Degree, Software Engineering 2009 - 2011



Bachelor of Science (BS), Software Engineering 2011 - 2013

# **Skills**

Linux • Programming • Voice over IP (VoIP) • DevOps • Internet Protocol Suite (TCP/IP) • Load Balancing • High Availability • Cluster Management • Scripting